

# Charles Kamiri

Full Stack Developer

- +254 797 317 704
- □ charleskamiri6@gmail.com
- ♀ Nairobi, Kenya
- @Charles Kamiri
- kamiri-charles.github.io/portfoliov2

## ABOUT ME

I am a passionate full stack software engineer specializing in frontend web design and backend app development. Growing up in a small town in the East African country of Kenya, I have always been interested in technology. This has led me to a passion for creating and building things that are useful and easy to use and yet have some complexity and uniqueness to them.

## EDUCATION

Business, Information and Technology St. Paul's University

2019 – 2022

Google UI/UX Developer

Coursera / JA Kenya 2021 - 2022

Web Development

FreeCodeCamp.org 2018 - 2019

**Backend Web Development** 

FreeCodeCamp.org 2018 - 2019

#### EXPERIENCE

Freelance Software Developer

Upwork, Remote, 2021 - current

Currently working in the freelance industry on the Upwork platform.

- Web Development. (React, Django, JavaScript)
- Frontend Design. (Figma, Adobe XD)
- 2D Game Development. (Pygame, JavaScript)

#### **Database Administrator**

St. Paul's University, Nairobi, 2019-2022

Worked as a database admin for the Nairobi campus dealing with student and staff data.

- PostgreSQL.
- PHP
- Java (Spring Boot)